Friends, now we will talk about III Lord
General Insurance Company Limited, whose
quarterly results have been declared today by the company. So let's
check
how the company's quarterly results are,
but before that, let's check
some fundamentals of the company. If friends talk about the
market cap of the company, then the
market cap of the company is ₹81000 227 crores, which is a
large cap company. After this, friends, if we talk about the
price to
earnings ratio of the company, it is 42.3, so
on seeing friends, the valuation of the company
seems a bit high here, but still we will check
where the valuation of the company stands in comparison with its peers.
If friends talk about ROI (
Return on Capital Employed) it is 22.5,
which is a very good ROI.
If friends talk about ROI (
Return on Invested Capital) it is
22.5, which is a very good
ROI. After that, friends, if we talk about debt
to equity ratio, then debt to equity
ratio friends, friends, it is 0.00.  Friends, the company
is a debt-free company and there is
no debt of any kind on the company here. After that,
friends, if we talk about promoter holding, then the
promoter holding is 47.9, which is
a good promoter holding. After that,
friends, if we talk about public holding, then the
public holding is 9.59, which is
a very good public holding. So,
overall, friends, if we talk about the fundamentals of the company,
then the fundamentals of the company are very
good. After this,
friends, let us see where the valuation of the company
stands in comparison to the top companies of its sector. If friends
talk about life insurance company, its PE
ratio is 15.30. If friends talk about
SBI Life Insurance, its PE ratio
is 78.7.6. If friends talk about HD FC
Life Insurance, its PE ratio is
85.31.
How is the performance here? First of all,
friends, let us talk about sales.
In the last quarter, friends, the
company had sales of Rs 5175 crore, which
increased to Rs
5367 crore in this quarter.  Sales have been made, so
quarter on quarter friends, there has been
growth in sales here. After this,
friends talk about net profit,
in the last quarter, friends, the
company had generated a net profit of 431 crores here, which has
increased to a net profit of 520 crores in this quarter. So,
quarter on quarter friends, the company has given a
very positive result here.
After this, friends talk about year on year
quarterly results and see
how the company performed here. If
friends talk about sales, then
in the same quarter last year, friends, there were
sales of 45001 crores here, which has
increased to 5367 crores in this quarter
here. So,
friends, there is growth quarter on quarter in sales
and year on year also there is
growth in sales here quarterly. After this,
friends talk about net profit,
in the same quarter last year, friends, a
net profit of 437 crores was generated here, which has
increased to 520 crores in this quarter this year, the
company has generated a net profit here
and within the net profit  Also
friends, there is growth here quarter on quarter
and year on year as well,
here in the net profit, friends, there has been
growth of the company, so overall friends,
if we talk about the result of quarter four, then the
result of quarter four, friends, friends, has been presented by the company here very
good and very positive.
After this,
friends, if we talk about the total assets of the company, then
compared to last year, the total assets of the company have
increased, which have increased
from 5586 to
63308, which is a
very good thing for the company. After this, if we
talk about cash flow, then cash from
operating activity friends, the cash
flow of the company is running positive here after March 2023
and anyway, friends, the
cash flow of the company is almost always positive,
which is a big
plus point for the company. Today, friends, if we talk about the
share holding pattern of the company, then in
this quarter, compared to the previous quarter, the
investment of friends has increased here, which was at 47.9
in the last quarter, the
holding of promoters here,
which has increased to 51.27 in this quarter.  But
here there is promoter holding
which is a very
good thing for the investors, after that friends let's talk about
public holding, in the last quarter
friends the public
holding was at 11.09, which has further reduced in this quarter and is
at 9.59,
which is also a very
good thing for the investors, so friends this was the
quarter four result of ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company, rest
how did you like my video, you
can tell us in the comment section, if you liked the
video friends then like my video
and if you want to see the results of quarter four in future also then
subscribe to my channel, thank you very much.